<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="card_description_main_interval_head">Main app config</string>
    <string name="card_description_main_interval_short">
        Default behavior is to do NOT ring if phone was in silence or vibrate-only mode before call (configurable)
    </string>
    <string name="card_description_main_interval_full">Number of seconds between two sound increase actions also affects vibrate and mute before ring option</string>

    <string name="card_description_config_min_max_head">Ringer volume limits</string>
    <string name="card_description_config_min_max_short">
        Allow to limit min and max ring volume
        \nSetting limit to 0 or -1 are for advanced max limit config.
        To enable mute/vibrate functions use suitable switch
    </string>
    <string name="card_description_config_min_max_full">
        When setting limit to prering value - check full description for \'Restore volume\'
    </string>

    <string name="card_description_restore_level_head">Restore volume after call</string>
    <string name="card_description_restore_level_short">Default behaviour is to restore pre-call level </string>
    <string name="card_description_restore_level_full">
        Be careful when you use this with max volume level limit = prering,
        because restore to 1 after call with max level = prering will give you no volume increase
    </string>

    <string name="card_description_vibrate_head">Vibration config</string>
    <string name="card_description_vibrate_short">
        Gives option to vibrate before ringing.
        Can cause vibration only with no ringtone without proper configuration.
        \nSee full description</string>
    <string name="card_description_vibrate_full">
        There are devices that do not support switch from mute/vibrate to normal ring mode during call.
        They stay vibrate-only even after volume increase.
        \nSolution is to use music stream instead ring stream. To do it you need to disable \'Use default playback stream\'.
        \nYou loose option to mute incoming ring with volume buttons but can mute with power button
        \nChanging stream can also change you max volume level. It usually happens if your max level was 7.
    </string>

    <string name="card_description_mute_head">Mute config</string>
    <string name="card_description_mute_short">
        Gives option to mute before ringing
        \nProbably will vibrate on android 5+ as mute is limited
        \nCan cause vibration only with no ringtone without proper configuration
    </string>
    <string name="card_description_mute_full">
        Can use LED notification for incall status
        \nPlease check vibrate config full description before you this
    </string>


    <string name="card_description_notification_head">Notification config</string>
    <string name="card_description_notification_short">
        Due to android os limitation LED works only while screen off
    </string>
    <string name="card_description_notification_full">
        Useful for upcoming silence mode
    </string>

    <string name="card_description_logging_head">Logging config</string>
    <string name="card_description_logging_short">
        Use it if you have problems or want to help in app development. Use buttons on last tab to send logs
    </string>
    <string name="card_description_logging_full">
        You can watch logging in realtime on Test page
    </string>

    <string name="card_description_keep_in_mem__head">Keep in memory</string>
    <string name="card_description_keep_in_mem_short">
        Will show app icon in notification area
        Keep app in memory to prevent being closed by memory cleaner
    </string>
    <string name="card_description_keep_in_mem_full">
        Low priority option hides icon from statusbar but increase chance of closing app when on low memory.
        \nA way to completely hide icon while function enabled is to go to system settings-> apps -> app -> notification option and disable notification for app.
        \nYou can take a looking at app restart evens in log to find out do you need to enable this function
    </string>

    <string name="card_description_ignore_silence_vibrate_head">Respect silence</string>
    <string name="card_description_ignore_silence_vibrate_short">
        Enabling this option force ring on incoming call when phone in mute or vibrate state.
        If you disabled this option but still have no ring when in vibrate mode
        please read the full description of the Vibrate config card then
    </string>
    <string name="card_description_ignore_silence_vibrate_full">
        You can also use this option in ase of  wrong mode detection: when software buttons on test page works ok but volume does not change on incoming ring.
        Use test page to check then
        \nPlease report if your phone need this option enabled
    </string>

    <string name="card_description_pause_wa_head">If restore volume does not work</string>
    <string name="card_description_pause_wa_short">
        Use it if your phone do not restore sound level after call. No need to disable
    </string>
    <string name="card_description_pause_wa_full">
        Reported devices:\n
        Nexus 5. Android 5.1.1 time reported = 1 sec
    </string>


    <string name="card_description_feedback_head">Feedback</string>
    <string name="card_description_feedback_short">
        Test page let you observe app in work
    </string>
    <string name="card_description_feedback_full">
        Upcoming features:
        \nMute incoming call with volume button when use music stream
        \nWidget for fast switch vibrate on and off
    </string>


    <string name="card_description_find_phone_head">Find phone</string>
    <string name="card_description_find_phone_short">
        Alter selected number of calls in row from same number within 5 minutes call will ring at max volume
    </string>
    <string name="card_description_find_phone_full">
        It helps you find phone when you live it somewhere in mute mode
    </string>

</resources>